[{"answer": "Break stuff", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I guess they're stupid", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well, yeah. Sort of. Nothing really mean. Me and my pals, me and my brothers. It was kind of funny then. Stealing pumpkins, soaping windows. Stuff like that", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "To us it was", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Some party, huh? Sorry I lost sight of you. I had to step outside for a smoke. You find anybody you know here? There must be some kids you used to know from school. You want to go tomorrow? See your old teachers? Be more fun than hanging out with me all day", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No what", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " my friend. Listen, my friend, tell you what. Tomorrow morning, you still want to go home, I'll drive you down. I'll get off work or something", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What? You called Mommy? Just now", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend, why", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Come and get you! Shit! It's a damn half hour drive each way. Why didn't you talk to me about it first", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Relax, Chief. We're leaving. You wanna toke", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Some job. Here, have a hit. Don't be such a hardass. I know you got problems, but everybody's got problems.", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Don't know about lucky. The guy's a ful", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend, he's always got some angle working. He wants to keep my friend happy, I'm his boy", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Done much shooting with that rifle yet", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "If you get it", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You understand what I'm saying? I want a deer, a dead one, not a cripple or whatthefuck", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "And you'll get your extra hundred bucks", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Said what", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Fuck. You don't know how bad or anything", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yes, my friend, I mean my friend. Put out that cigarette. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " A half mile in, along the old lumber road", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "The ambulance guys lugged him up", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Saw him do it", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You musta seen him get shot. I know you did", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Yeah", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "He sure as hell won't", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I get to feeling like a whipped dog some days, my friend, and some night I'm going to bite back. I swear it", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No, no, I haven't. Not really. I've growled a little, but I haven't bit", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Oh, my friend", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You've been married twice", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I think your first response to the Twombley shooting was the correct one", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "That it wasn't an accident", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "It's pretty old", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Pop", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "my friend, please, it's alright. Nothing happened", "docId": "Affliction.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " Okay, let's go home, then", "qsentId": 38}]